Inventory of the James A. Bill Papers 1940-2003
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Collection of Dissertations and Theses, 1975-1987
  - Dissertations and Theses Dedicated to, and Supervised by James A. Bill (1)
    - (1, 33)
      - Daoudi, Mohammed S. “The Politactics of International Cartels: Economic Illusions, Political Realities, and OPEC.” Diss. U. of Texas at Austin, 1984 (1, 33)
      - Anurugsa, Panomporn. “Political Integration Policy in Thailand: The Case of the Malay Muslim Minority.” Diss. U. of Texas at Austin, 1984 (1, 33)
      - Koenig, Edna Louise. “The Nation Building of Tanzania: An Interaction Approach.” Thesis. U. of Texas at Austin, 1970 (1, 33)
      - Natto, Ibrahim Abbas. “Local Administration in Mecca.” Thesis. U. of Texas at Austin, 1970 (1, 33)
      - Lutz, James Michael. “Military and Civilian Regimes in Sub - Saharan Africa Comparisons, Differences, and Similarities.” Thesis. U. of Texas at Austin, 1972 (1, 33)
      - Howell, Robert E. “Student Political Protest in Japan: Possible Causes and Implications.” Thesis. U. of Texas at Austin, 1970 (1, 33)
      - Al - Ghabra, Shafeeq N. “Palestinians in Kuwait: The Family and Politics of Survival.” Diss. U. of Texas at Austin, 1987 (1, 33)
      - Brunson, Yvonne Marie. “An Assessment of Saudi Arabia’s Endeavor to Modernize, In the Context of Declining Oil Revenues and Islamic Fundamentalism.” Diss. U. of Texas at Austin, 1985 (1, 33)
      - Sonn, Ho Chul. “A Comparative Study of Social Revolutions: China and Vietnam.” Diss. U. of Texas at Austin, 1982 (1, 33)
  Series 13: Interviews Conducted by James Bill on Cassette Tape
- Interviews Conducted by James Bill on Cassette Tape, 1988-1993
  Contains cassette tapes concerning interviews conducted by James Bill of various people, 1988-1993, including George Ball, Robert Schaetzel, W. W. Rostow, Michael Blumenthal, Roger Hilsman, Donald Lamm, Peter Peterson, Helen Vahey, William Bundy, Nicholas Katzenbach, J. Wm. Fulbright, Arthur Hartman, Roger L. Stevens, James Schlesinger, George Springsteen, Paul Nitze, Douglas Ball, Lucius Battle, David Rockefeller, John Tuthill, George McGhee, Dean Rusk, and Ruth Ball.
  - (34)
      Subseries 1: Interview # 1: September 14, 1988
    - Interview # 1: September 14, 1988 (34, 1)
      - Tape 1: A, B - George Ball (34, 1)
      - Tape 2: A - George Ball (34, 1)
      Subseries 2: Interview # 2: February 17, 1989
    - Interview # 2: February 17, 1989 (34, 2)
      - Tape 3:A,B - George Ball, Douglas Ball (34, 2)
      - Tape 4:A, B – George Ball, Douglas Ball (34, 2)
      Subseries 3: Interview # 3: February 18, 1989
    - Interview # 3: February 18, 1989 (34, 3)
      - Tape 5: A - George Ball, Douglas Ball (34, 3)
      - Tape 5:B - George Ball, Ruth Ball (34, 3)
      - Tape 6:A - Ruth Ball (34, 3)
      - Tape 6:B - Ruth Ball, George Ball (34, 3)
      Subseries 4: Interview # 4: September 16, 1989
    - Interview # 4: September 16, 1989 (34, 4)
        Series 1: Tape 7: A,B - George Ball
      - Tape 7: A,B - George Ball (34, 4)
        Series 2: Tape 8: A,B - George Ball
      - Tape 8: A,B - George Ball (34, 4)
        Series 3: Tape 9: A,B - Douglas Ball
      - Tape 9: A,B - Douglas Ball (34, 4)
      Subseries 5: Interview # 5: October 14, 1989
    - Interview # 5: October 14, 1989 (34, 5)
      - Tape 10:A,B - George Ball (34, 5)
      Subseries 6: Interview # 6: November 6, 1989
    - Interview # 6: November 6, 1989 (34, 6)
      - Tape 11: A,B - Dean Rusk (34, 6)
      Subseries 7: Interview # 7: January 27, 1990
    - Interview # 7: January 27, 1990 (34, 7)
        Series 1: Tape 12:A, B - George Ball
      - Tape 12:A, B - George Ball (34, 7)
      Subseries 8: Interview # 8: January 28, 1990
    - Interview # 8: January 28, 1990 (34, 8)
      - Tape 13: A, B - Douglas Ball (34, 8)
      - Tape 14: A, B - Douglas Ball (34, 8)
      Subseries 9: Interview # 9: February 14, 1990
    - Interview # 9: February 14, 1990 (34, 9)
      - Tape 15: A, B - George McGhee (34, 9)
      - Tape 16: A - George McGhee (34, 9)
      Subseries 10: Interview # 10: April 17, 1990
    - Interview # 10: April 17, 1990 (34, 10)
      - Tape 17: A, B - Amb. John Tuthill (34, 10)
      Subseries 11: Interview # 11: November 9, 1990
    - Interview # 11: November 9, 1990 (34, 11)
      - Tape 18: A - David Rockefeller (34, 11)
      Subseries 12: Interview # 12: April 26, 1991
    - Interview # 12: April 26, 1991 (34, 12)
      - Tape 19: A - George Ball (34, 12)
      Subseries 13: Interview # 13: August 27, 1991
    - Interview # 13: August 27, 1991 (34, 13)
      - Tape 20: A, B - Amb. Lucius Battle (34, 13)
      Subseries 14: Interview # 14: September 4, 1991
    - Interview # 14: September 4, 1991 (34, 14)
      - Tape 21: A,B - George Ball, Douglas Ball (34, 14)
      - Tape 22: A - George Ball, Douglas Ball (34, 14)
      Subseries 15: Interview # 15: October 12, 1991
    - Interview # 15: October 12, 1991 (34, 15)
      - Tape 23: A, B - George Ball (34, 15)
      Subseries 16: Interview # 16: November 12, 1991
    - Interview # 16: November 12, 1991 (34, 16)
      - Tape 24: A, B - Paul Nitze (34, 16)
      Subseries 17: Interview # 17: November 12, 1991
    - Interview # 17: November 12, 1991 (34, 17)
      - Tape 25: A, B - George Springsteen (34, 17)
      Subseries 18: Interview # 18: November 12, 1991
    - Interview # 18: November 12, 1991 (34, 18)
      - Tape 26: A - James Schlesinger; Commentary on the Three 11/12/91 Interviews (34, 18)
      Subseries 19: Interview # 19: November 13, 1991
    - Interview # 19: November 13, 1991 (34, 19)
      - Tape 27: B – Roger L. Stevens (34, 19)
      - Tape 27: A - Roger L. Steves/Commentary (34, 19)
      Subseries 20: Interview # 20: November 13, 1991
    - Interview # 20: November 13, 1991 (34, 20)
      - Tape 28: A, B - Arthur Hartman (34, 20)
      Subseries 21: Interview # 21: November 25, 1991
    - Interview # 21: November 25, 1991 (34, 21)
      - Tape 29: A - Sen. J. Wm. Fulbright (34, 21)
      - Tape 29: B - Sen. J. Wm. Fulbright/ Commentary (34, 21)
      Subseries 22: Interview # 22: December 13, 1991
    - Interview # 22: December 13, 1991 (34, 22)
      - Tape 30: A - George Ball (34, 22)
      Subseries 23: Interview # 23: December 13, 1991
    - Interview # 23: December 13, 1991 (34, 23)
      - Tape 31: A, B - Nicholas Katzenbac (34, 23)
      Subseries 24: Interview # 24: December 1991
    - Interview # 24: December 1991 (34, 24)
      - Tape 32: A, B - William Bundy (34, 24)
      Subseries 25: Interview # 25: January 7, 1992
    - Interview # 25: January 7, 1992 (34, 25)
      - Tape 33: A, B - Helen Vahey (34, 25)
      Subseries 26: Interview # 26: January 8, 1992
    - Interview # 26: January 8, 1992 (34, 26)
      - Tape 34: A, B - Peter Peterson (34, 26)
      - Tape 35: A - Peter Peterson (34, 26)
      Subseries 27: Interview # 27: January 10, 1992
    - Interview # 27: January 10, 1992 (34, 27)
      - Tape 36: A, B - Donald Lamm (34, 27)
      Subseries 28: Interview # 28: January 12, 1992
    - Interview # 28: January 12, 1992 (34, 28)
      - Tape 37: A, B - Roger Hilsman (34, 28)
      - Tape 38: A - Roger Hilsman (34, 28)
      Subseries 29: Interview # 29: January 14, 1992
    - Interview # 29: January 14, 1992 (34, 29)
      Subseries 30: Interview # 30: February 4, 1992
    - Interview # 30: February 4, 1992 (34, 30)
      - Tape 40: A, B - W. W. Rostow (34, 30)
      Subseries 31: Interview # 31: February 11, 1992
    - Interview # 31: February 11, 1992 (34, 31)
      - Tape 41: A, B - Robert Schaetzel (34, 31)
      Subseries 32: Interview # 32: March 12, 1993
    - Interview # 32: March 12, 1993 (34, 32)
      - Tape 42: A, B - George Ball (34, 32)
  Series 14: Bilderberg Meetings and Conferences Books and Papers
- Bilderberg Meetings and Conferences Books and Papers, 1954-1988
  - (35)
      Subseries 1: Bilderberg Meetings and Conference Books, 27 books from 1954 - 1988
    - Bilderberg Meetings and Conference Books, 27 books from 1954 - 1988 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Conference. May 29th – 31st, 1954 (35, 1)
      - Barbizon Conference. March 18th – 20th, 1955 (35, 1)
      - Garmish - Partenkirchen Conference. September 23 - 25, 1955 (35, 1)
      - Fiuggi Conference. October 4 - 6, 1957 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Group. St. Simons Island Conference. February 15 - 17, 1957 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Group. Buxton Conference. September 13 - 15, 1958 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Group. Yesilkoy Conference. September 18 - 20, 1959 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. Villa D’este Conference. April 2 - 4, 1965 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. Wiesbaden Conference. March 25 - 27, 1966 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. Cambridge Conference. 31 March – 2 April, 1967 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. Marienlyst Conference. 9 - 11 May 1969 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. Bad Ragaz. 17, 18 and 19 April 1970. Notice for Participants (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. Bad Ragaz. 17 - 19 April 1970 [5 copies] (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. The Hague. List of Participants. August 1970 [3 copies] (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. Woodstock Conference. 23 - 25 April 1971 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. Knokee Conference. 21 - 23 April 1972 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. Saltsjobaden Conference. 11 - 13 May 1973 [2 copies] (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. Burgenstock Conference. 15 - 17 May 1981 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. Chateau Montebello Conference. 13 - 15 May 1983 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. Telfs - Buchen Conference. 3 - 5 June 1988 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. List of Participants. August 1970 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. List of Participants. August 1970 (35, 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings. List of Participants. March 1970 [pamphlet] (35, 1)
  Series 15: Henry Kissinger Paper and Reports
- Henry Kissinger Paper and Reports, 1974-1989
    Subseries 1: Foreign Relations Reports and Papers of and Concerning Henry Kissinger
  - Foreign Relations Reports and Papers of and Concerning Henry Kissinger (1)
    - (1, 35)
        Subseries 1: Kissinger and Foreign Relations Reports, 1974
      - Kissinger and Foreign Relations Reports, 1974 (1, 35)
        - (1, 35)
          - Sonnefeldt, April 2, 1974 (no attribution) (1, 35)
          - Sisco, Joseph J., March 27, 1974 (background) (1, 35)
          - Rodman, Peter., National Security Council, March 29, 1974 (not attribution – very skittish) (1, 35)
          - McCloskey, Robert., March 25, 1974 (background) (1, 35)
          - Lord, Winston., March 23, 1974 (1, 35)
          - Rush, Kenneth. Deputy Secretary of State. In two meetings, March 27 and 28, 1974 (1, 35)
          - Unknown author. March 25, 1974 (1, 35)
          - Unknown author. Reflection on Henry Kissinger’s actions. (1, 35)
        Subseries 2: Coorespondences between George Ball and Henry Kissinger
      - Coorespondences between George Ball and Henry Kissinger (1, 35, 2)
        - (1, 35, 2)
          - Ball, George. To Henry Kissinger. November 18, 1976 (1, 35, 2)
          - Kissinger, Henry. To George Ball. December 6, 1976 (1, 35, 2)
          - Kissinger, Henry. To George Ball. September 27, 1974 [memorandum] (1, 35, 2)
          - Kissinger, Henry. To George Ball. March 29, 1973 [memorandum] (1, 35, 2)
          - Kissinger, Henry. To George Ball. May 21, 1971 (1, 35, 2)
          - Richards, Bill. “Ball Asserts Kissinger’s ‘Obnoxious’ Pressure Preceded Entry of Shah.” The Washington Post. 26 Nov. 1979 (1, 35, 2)
            - Ball, George. “Letters: Kissinger on Iran.” The Economist. 17 Feb. 1979 (1, 35, 2)
          - Kissinger, Henry. To George Ball. December 11, 1968 (1, 35, 2)
          - Lewis, Anthony. “Mr. Kissinger’s Role.” New York Times. 26 Nov. 1979 (1, 35, 2)
          - Falk, Richard. “Carter’s Courtier: Brzezinski: Looking out for #1.” The Nation. 27 Sept. 1980. (1, 35, 2)
          - Nickel, Herman. “Why ‘Zbig’ is Not Quite on Top of the World.” Fortune. 23 April 1979 pp. 71 - 75 (1, 35, 2)
          - Peterson, Peter. To David Rockefeller. July 16, 1981 (1, 35, 2)
          - Draft of a letter to David [surname unknown]. August 10, 1981 – written on header “to Peterson 8/10/1981 (1, 35, 2)
          - Kissinger, Henry. To George Ball. June 5, 1985 (1, 35, 2)
          - Ball, George. To Henry Kissinger. February 14, 1989 (1, 35, 2)
          - Kissinger, Henry. To George Ball. March 21, 1989 (1, 35, 2)
          - Ball, George. To Henry Kissinger. June 11, 1985 (1, 35, 2)
          - Hewitt, Don (executive producer of NBC). To George Ball. [date unknown] (1, 35, 2)
            - Hewitt, Don. To Henry Kissinger. April 30, 1980 (1, 35, 2)
          - Kissinger, Henry. To William Leonard. May 6, 1980 [10 pages] (1, 35, 2)
            - Kissinger, Henry. To Dan Rather. May 1, 1980 (1, 35, 2)
          - Kissinger, Henry. To George Ball. November 2, 1986 (1, 35, 2)
          - Kissinger, Henry. To Bill Leanord. May 9, 1980 (1, 35, 2)
            - Leonard, Bill. To Henry Kissinger. May 16, 1980 (1, 35, 2)
        Subseries 3: Newspapers, magazine articles and essays concerning Kissinger and Iran.
      - Newspapers, magazine articles and essays concerning Kissinger and Iran. (1, 35, 3)
        - (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - Ball, George. “Scathing Re - examination Leave Kissinger Tarnished, but not Demolished.” The Christian Science Monitor. 2 Sept. 1983 B5 (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - Mcgrory, Mary. “Who Wants the Shah Here?: Dr. K has it both ways.” New York Post. 27 November 1979 (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - Copy: McGrory, Mary. “Carter may replace Sullivan to signal ‘new start’ in Iran.” New York Post. 20 February 1979 (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - Burt, Richard. “U.S. Strategy on Iran Stirs a Fierce Debate.” New York Times. 12 January 1979. A.3 (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - Gwertzman, Bernard. “Stresses a Trip Would Be Temporary, but Return Is Viewed as Difficult.” New York Times. 9 January 1979. A. 1. glued onto paper (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - Essay: “Iran’s Current Problems and Needs as they Confront the United States: Economic, Social, Intellectual and Moral Concerns” General Introduction. (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - “Showdown for the Shah.” Newsweek. 20 November 1978. p. 58 - 68. Glued onto paper. (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - “Human Rights Policy Behind Unrest - Kissinger.” Keyhan International. 4 November 1978. p.1 (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - Hersh, Seymour M. “Brzezinski Is Said to Have Rejected Warnings About Problem in Iran.” New York Times. 21 December 1978. A.1 (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - Schmidt, Dana Adams. “New CIA Tale: Kurd Leader Was Secretely Flown to U.S.” Christian Science Monitor. 3 November 1975. p. 3. (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - Clarity, James F. “Iran’s Help to Kurds Fighting Iraq Includes Arm(s).” New York Times. 11 October 1974.pg 12 (Copy) (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - Schmidt, Dana Adams. “Iranian aid vital to Kurds.” The Christian Science Monitor. 12 December 1974. p. 4 (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - “Shah Says Ancient Differences With Iraq Are Over.” 8 March 1975. (Copy). (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - “Iraq - Iran Accord and Impact on Gulf.” The Arab World Weekly. 15 March 1975. p. 5 - 9. (Copy) (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - Namvar, Majid. “Iranian Stalinists Hail Shah’s Betrayal of Kurds.” Intercontinental Press. 22 January 1975. (Copy) (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - Lieber, Robert J. “Costs of Amorality: A ‘Political Science Lecture’.” Commentary: Harper’s. p. 77 - 78 (1, 35, 3, 2)
          - Personal Message. Henry Kissinger to Hon. George Ball. September 29 (1, 35, 3, 2)
  Series 16: International Iran Times Newspapers
- International Iran Times Newspapers, 2004-2006
  - (35)
      Subseries 1: International Iran Times Newspapers 2004-2007
    - International Iran Times Newspapers 2004-2007 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 13, 16 June 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 14, 23 June 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 11, 2 June 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 12, 9 June 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 16, 7 June 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 15, 30 June 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 17, 14 July 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 21, 11 Aug. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 18, 21 June 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 22, 18 Aug. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 20, 4 Aug. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 27, 22 Sept. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 26, 15 Sept. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 23, 25 Aug. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 24, 1 Sept. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 25, 8 Sept 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 44, 19 Sept. 2007 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 45, 26 Sept. 2007 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 43, 12 Jan. 2007 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 42, 5 Jan. 2007 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 40, 22 Dec. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 28, 29 Sept 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 29, 6 Oct. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 30, 13 Oct. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 34, 10 Nov. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 33, 3 Nov. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 32, 27 Oct. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 39, 10 Dec. 2004 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 35, 17 Nov. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 38, 3 Dece. 2004 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 37, 26 Nov. 2004 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 36, 19 Nov. 2004 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 36, 24 Nov. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 38, 8 Dec. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 37, 1 Dec. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 39, 15 Dec. 2006 (35, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 19, 28 July 2006 (35, 1)
  - (36)
      Subseries 1: International Iran Times 2004 - 2006
    - International Iran Times 2004 - 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 51, 4 March 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 52, 11 March 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 1, 25 March 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 2, 1 April 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 3, 8 April 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 4, 15 April 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 5, 22 April 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 6, 29 April 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 7, 6 May 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 8, 13 May 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 11, 28 May, 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 12, 4 June 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 13, 11 June 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 14, 18 June 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 15, 25 June 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 16, 2 July 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 17, 9 July 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 18, 16 July 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 19, 23 July 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 21, 6 Aug. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 22, 13 Aug. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 23, 20 Aug. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 24, 27 Aug. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 25, 3 Sept. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 27, 17 Sept. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 29, 1 Oct. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 30, 8 Oct. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 32, 22 Oct. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 31, 15 Oct. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 33, 29 Oct. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 34, 5 Nov. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 35, 12 Nov. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 26, 10 Sept. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 28, 24 Sept. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 40, 17 Dec. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 41, 24 Dec 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 42, 31 Dec. 2004 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 43, 7 Jan. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 44, 14 Jan. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 46, 28 Jan. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 45, 21 Jan. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 47, 4 Feb. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 48, 11 Feb. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 49, 18 Feb. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 34, no. 50, 25 Feb. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 9, 20 May, 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 10, 27 May 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 16, 8 July 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 17, 15 July 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 18, 22 July 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 19, 29 July 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 20, 5 Aug. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 21, 12 Aug. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 22, 19 Aug. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 23, 26 Aug. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 24, 2 Sept. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 25, 9 Sept. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 26, 16 Sept. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 27, 23 Sept. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 28, 30 Sept. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 29, 7 Oct. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 30, 14 Oct. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 31, 21 Oct. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 32, 28 Oct. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 33, 4 Nov. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 34, 11 Nov. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 35, 18 Nov. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 36, 25 Nov. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 37, 2 Dec. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 38, 9 Dec. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 39, 16 Dec. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 41, 30 Dec. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 40, 23 Dec. 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 43, 13 Jan. 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 42, 6 Jan. 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 44, 20 Jan. 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 45, 27 Jan. 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 12, 10 June 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 11, 3 June 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 14, 24 June 2005 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 47, 10 Feb. 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 46, 3 Feb. 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 50, 3 March 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 51, 10 March 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 48, 17 Feb. 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 52, 17 March, 2006 [in farsi] (36, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 1, 24 March 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 52, 17 March 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 3, 17 April 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 2, 31 March 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 4, 14 Friday 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 5, 21 April 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 7, 5 May, 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 6, 28 April 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 8, 12 May 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 36, no. 9, 19 May 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 49, 24 Feb. 2006 (36, 1)
      - Vol. 35, no. 10, 26 May 2006 (36, 1)
      Subseries 2: Century Club Luncheon Files, 1990 – 1988
    - Century Club Luncheon Files, 1990 – 1988 (36, 2)
      Subseries 3: Princeton University – George Ball Collection
    - Princeton University – George Ball Collection (36, 3)
      Subseries 4: Bilderberg Photos – 1993
    - Bilderberg Photos – 1993 (36, 4)
      Subseries 5: Lloyd Cutler Coorespondances
    - Lloyd Cutler Coorespondances (36, 5)
      Subseries 6: George Ball Authored Articles on Free Trade
    - George Ball Authored Articles on Free Trade (36, 6)
      Subseries 7: Bilderberg Meeting Notices and Topic Information
    - Bilderberg Meeting Notices and Topic Information (36, 7)
      Subseries 8: Schuman Plan Documents/Analysis and Explanations (In French)
    - Schuman Plan Documents/Analysis and Explanations (In French) (36, 8)
      Subseries 9: George Ball Coorespondance Copies, 1951
    - George Ball Coorespondance Copies, 1951 (36, 9)
      Subseries 10: Newspaper Articles Concerning David Rockefeller
    - Newspaper Articles Concerning David Rockefeller (36, 10)
      Subseries 11: James Bill Coorespondances and Miscellanious Bilderberg Documents
    - James Bill Coorespondances and Miscellanious Bilderberg Documents (36, 11)
      Subseries 12: Materials Concerning James Bill’s work on George Ball
    - Materials Concerning James Bill’s work on George Ball (36, 12)
      Subseries 13: Newspapers, and Materials Concerning Bilderberg Meetings and George Ball
    - Newspapers, and Materials Concerning Bilderberg Meetings and George Ball (36, 13)